imgstudio.com 2000-08-23

# Privacy Policy of Imgstudio

|  **  
PRIVACY POLICY  
**   
_General Philosophy_ :   
1)Imgstudio believes that personal information and privacy of it's Members must be respected. As the personal information you hereby impart may impact you in a number of ways, Imgstudio is committed towards respecting your privacy.   
2)Any information provided or obtained by Imgstudio regarding you and/ or your session may be used to improve our Site and the services being offered to you.   
3)A cookie may be assigned to your internet browser to track your user's session. Imgstudio may analyse this data for certain trends and statistics.   
4)In order to protect your privacy we have inter alia prohibited the following activities:   
(i) Use the Site in connection with unauthorised surveys, contests, pyramid schemes, chain letters, junk email, spamming or any duplicative or unsolicited messages (commercial or otherwise).   
(ii) Any act, deed or thing that would defame, abuse, harass, stalk, threaten or otherwise violate the legal rights (such as rights of privacy and publicity) of others including the rights of Imgstudio in relation to the service or the contents thereof.   
(iii) Imgstudio has the right to immediately terminate any membership which it believes, in its sole discretion, is responsible for transmitting or is otherwise connected with any spam or other unsolicited bulk email or any illegal activity or any infringement of any third party right including without limitation any intellectual property right or in contravention of any term, condition or obligation of the TOS.   
5)If you have any questions or comments about our privacy practices or would like to correct or update information provided to Imgstudio via its Website, please contact us by either clicking on the feedback button or by sending an e-mail to _contact@imgstudio.com_. 

**Cookies:**   
To enable some of the services we offer or procure to be offered to you we may assign "cookies" to your internet browser. A cookie is a small data/ text file that certain Web sites write to your hard drive when you visit them. A cookie file can contain information such as user identification that is stored on your computer and used by the Site to track the pages you have visited. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Imgstudio proposes to use cookies to track user traffic patterns (as described above) and such other personal information that you may provide.

|  |   | **  
****Register Now| Login** |    
---|---|---  
  | _  
_ |    
  |    
|    
  | **Search Tips** |
